<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>HAX11TY doc site</title>
  <link href="https://deepdivetech.github.io/hax11ty/atom.xml" rel="self" />
  <subtitle>HAX + 11ty = bliss</subtitle>
  <updated>2021-02-25T19:23:13.325+00:00</updated>
  <author>
      <name>EdTechJoker</name>
  </author>
  <id>https://deepdivetech.github.io/hax11ty/atom.xml</id>
  <entry>
    <title>About</title>
    <id>https://deepdivetech.github.io/hax11ty/content/1_about/</id>
    <updated>2021-02-25T19:23:13.325+00:00</updated>
    <published>2021-02-25T19:23:13.325+00:00</published>
    <summary></summary>
    <link href="https://deepdivetech.github.io/hax11ty/content/1_about/"/>
    <content type="html">
      &lt;p&gt;HAX11ty is a merger between HAX and 11ty. It uses these technologies in the following way:
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;User edits via HAX (future) or modifies files locally&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;hax11ty script watches for changes and rebuilds files w/ 11ty, refreshing the screen&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;this is compiled to a valid HAXcms data package to be used either completely static with a CDN or locally in HAXcms PHP version&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Installation</title>
    <id>https://deepdivetech.github.io/hax11ty/content/2_install/</id>
    <updated>2021-02-25T19:23:13.325+00:00</updated>
    <published>2021-02-25T19:23:13.325+00:00</published>
    <summary></summary>
    <link href="https://deepdivetech.github.io/hax11ty/content/2_install/"/>
    <content type="html">
      &lt;code-sample copy-clipboard-button&gt;
&lt;template&gt;
  git clone https://github.com/elmsln/hax11ty.git
  cd hax11ty
  yarn install
  yarn start
&lt;/template&gt;
&lt;/code-sample&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the fastest way to get up and running. If you instead want to build new sites with this and push them back up to gh-pages rapidly, start by &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/elmsln/hax11ty/generate&quot;&gt;using this repo as a template&lt;/a&gt;. This will copy the github actions workflows as well so all you need to do is change our repo in the git clone above to yours in order to start on what will easily become a live website!&lt;/p&gt;

    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Why HAX11ty</title>
    <id>https://deepdivetech.github.io/hax11ty/content/3_why/</id>
    <updated>2021-02-25T19:23:13.325+00:00</updated>
    <published>2021-02-25T19:23:13.325+00:00</published>
    <summary></summary>
    <link href="https://deepdivetech.github.io/hax11ty/content/3_why/"/>
    <content type="html">
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Power of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.11ty.dev/&quot;&gt;11ty&lt;/a&gt; for publishing static / high SEO&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Easier than 11ty, 0 config solution for publishing&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Power of HAXcms for rocket fast PWA in a forever format&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Extendable via web components&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://haxtheweb.org&quot;&gt;HAX&lt;/a&gt; as web editor to skip markdown&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Easy github pages based publishing workflow&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;All files requiring change are in &lt;code&gt;src/&lt;/code&gt; directory&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Output can plug into &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/elmsln/haxcms&quot;&gt;HAXcms SaaS&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/elmsln/haxiam&quot;&gt;HAXcms PaaS&lt;/a&gt; solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;High lighthouse scores are achieved with certain constraints that will keep it from hitting max possible scores:
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;We keep things unbundled to allow for maximal reuse. This has an initial performance hit in the name of page to page speed.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;We do this so that if you put, for example, meme-maker into a page of content, hax11ty will generate the preload statements for that element from the CDN. This is done on a page by page level.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;That&#39;s it. All other mettrics we can hit the same scores as any other app!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <id>https://deepdivetech.github.io/hax11ty/content/Welcome World/</id>
    <updated>2021-02-25T19:23:13.325+00:00</updated>
    <published>2021-02-25T19:23:13.325+00:00</published>
    <summary></summary>
    <link href="https://deepdivetech.github.io/hax11ty/content/Welcome World/"/>
    <content type="html">
      &lt;p&gt;Hello world,&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I welcome you to my first blog post and I hope you get something out of it.&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who Am I?&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Lee and I’m behind the mask of Deep Dive Tech. I am a senior (very sad, I’ll cry later though) at Pennsylvania State University. My major is Telecommunications (think of cell phones) and I have a minor in Information Science &amp; Technology. Not really sure what career path I would want to pursue after graduation. However, I am hoping to get into Networking, maybe pursue to be a Network Technician or go another route in Project Management. I’m sure I can maybe get a taste of both in one job farther down the road, but I will be grateful to whatever company decides to take a chance on me.&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My Current and Past Experiences…&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve always been into technology ever since I got my first computer at a young age. Something about technology and how it enhances a human life is very satisfying to me. The one piece of technology I like so much is smartphones. It is surely amazing seeing how far we’ve come with the evolution of a cellular device.&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My attraction to these life changing devices drove me to become a sales specialist for Verizon Wireless the summer of 2018. My experience through working for a company like Verizon really taught me a lot about phones (despite stressing out on hitting your monthly numbers for commission). It really solidified my interest in the tech world even more, but I want to dig DEEPER.&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since then, I’ve experienced great opportunities such as being an Optics Development Engineer for a TV advertising company Ampersand based in New York, New York. Even though I will most likely not end up in the TV advertising industry, the experience of being an engineer for this company was such a great experience nonetheless.&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, on top going to school at Penn State, I am studying for my Comp TIA Network+ certification. This is not an easy task, but with effective studying I will be able to know the basics in and out of networking such as having knowledge in routers, switches, protocols, etc. I am excited to see where life takes me and hope I begin my tech career in a good environment where I can grow as a tech professional, as well as being the best person I can be.&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So What’s Next?&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a lot of things I would consider I’m passionate about. But, I can’t say there’s one particular topic in tech specifically that I am extremely passionate about. If there’s one thing for certain with technology though it would have to be security is one of my biggest interests. One thing that gets to me the most with using the Internet is that it targets you for advertisements or a potential threat to access personal information. To debut my Deep Dive Tech youtube page, I will show what privacy extensions for Google Chrome is best to protect yourself. Enjoy!&lt;p&gt;

    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>